Gus Russo papers, Inclusive: 1932-2006, Bulk: 1953-1998
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Gus Russo papers
Inclusive: 1932-2006, Bulk: 1953-1998
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
98
Russo, Gus, 1950 -
43 document boxes
The Gus Russo papers contain notes, clippings, publications, and other research materials related to the John F. Kennedy assassination and Russo's publication of Live by the Sword: The Secret War Against Castro and the Death of JFK.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Gus Russo, investigative journalist, author, and musician, was born in Baltimore, Maryland. He attended Mount St. Joseph High School. Although known for his research of the Kennedy assassination, music was his first passion. Russo explains, “I love to read, but I never thought I’d be a writer. But when you think about it, writing is very much like music: it’s all about the rhythm, the dynamics, the feeling - it’s all about flow. I spent my whole life as a musician. I guess that translates.” Russo keeps up both interests, boasting a successful writing career in which he published 6 nonfiction books, and as professional musician/producer.
As a young man he was active politically, opposing the Vietnam War and working for Robert Kennedy in the 1968 Presidential Campaign. His interest in the Kennedy assassination began at an early age. Russo describes his memories of the assassination: “I was in the hallway before 8th period, Mr. Hall’s biology class. Just going down the hall and there was a whisper, ‘Did you hear? Kennedy’s been shot.’ELWe went to our homeroom and then the announcement came that he was dead. A room full of boys and half of them were crying.” Thirty years later, Russo was one of two leading reporters on the documentary Who Was Lee Harvey Oswald? The Public Broadcasting Service (PBS) project aired in 1993 and was an unforgettable experience for Russo. He recalls, “With a huge research budget, we divided into four teams. All of us were given great latitude. I was allowed to follow up on every lead (conspiratorial and otherwise) I had always wanted to test. We went everywhere Oswald went, from Minsk, Russia to Atsugi, Japan. I crisscrossed the US for eighteen months.” That same year, Dan Rather selected Russo to appear on his TV special Who Shot JFK? Russo also found work with ABC News and Peter Jennings for the piece, “Dangerous World, The Kennedy Years.”
In 1998, Russo published Live by the Sword: The Secret War Against Castro and the Death of JFK, which was nominated for a Pulitzer Prize. In 2008, Brothers In Arms: The Kennedys, Castros, and the Politics of Murder was released and awarded the 2008 History Prize by the New York Book Festival. In 2011, Russo looked introspectively and published his autobiography, Boomer Days.
As the 50th anniversary of the assassination approached, Russo’s friend and 60 Minutes Producer, Harry Moses, reached out to him. They partnered with Tom Brokaw and NBC and devised an idea for a documentary. Where Were You? features the stories of everyday Americans and their recollections of November 22, 1963. With only four weeks to prepare, Russo explained, “It’s really tough to do something like this in a very short period of time. With any of these [documentary] shows, you film people for an hour and you use about eight seconds. It’s frustrating having an hour of great material whittled down to a few seconds, especially something as emotional as this.” To do the project justice, a companion guide to feature the full interviews would be published. The program aired on NBC on November 22, 2013.
Scope and Content
The Gus Russo papers range from 1932-2006, with dates representing both primary and secondary source documents which make up Russo’s research. Materials are related to his 1998 publication of Live by the Sword: The Secret War Against Castro and the Death of JFK. These are organized topically or by name, and include newspaper clippings, government documents, publications, and other research material related to the Kennedy assassination. Additionally, most of the folders in Boxes 33-35 are testimonials before the House of Representatives Select Committee on Assassinations.
Arrangement
The Gus Russo papers were accompanied by an inventory prior to current processing. The folders have largely been kept in the order in which Russo left them. Most of the folder titles have been altered for clarity and are indicative of the materials in the folders, following the patterns set down by Russo whenever possible. Russo often made notes on the folders themselves. These notes have been photocopied, marked as such, and placed in the appropriate folder. These notes often supply connections to other folders or subjects which might be beneficial to the researcher. The papers as a whole are arranged by folder title, which are organized by topic or individual name.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 98. Acquired 2013-04-01
Related Resources
Related references
"About Gus Russo,” and "About Live by the Sword." Bancroft Press. 2004.
Baughman, Julie. “Catonsville Resident Gus Russo Honors Memories of JFK Assassination 50 Years Later." Baltimore Sun. November 5, 2013.
Simkin, John. “Gus Russo.” Spartacus Educational. August 2014.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Castro, Fidel, 1926-; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 -- Assassination.; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968.; Oswald, Lee Harvey.; Russo, Gus -- Archives.; Russo, Gus. Live by the sword.
Places
Cuba -- Foreign relations -- United States.; Cuba -- History -- Invasion, 1961.; United States -- Foreign relations -- 1953-1961.
Subjects
United States -- Foreign Relations -- Cuba.
Genres
Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Government publications.
- Sierra-Martinez, Paulino, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Reboso, Manuel A., undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Rodriguez, Felix I., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Sanchez-Arango, Aureliano, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Rojas-Villanueva, Ylario, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Diaz, Nino, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Quintero, Raphael, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Messer, Nilo, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Kennedy, Robert Francis + Cuba, c.1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Kennedy, Robert Francis Cuba, Files, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Kennedy, Robert Francis, Logs, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Fair Play for Cuba Committee (FPCC), 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Kennedy, Angelo, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- CIA + Cubans, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- AMWORLD (Plan for a coup in Cuba), 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- CIA Microfilm Records, House Select Committee on Assassination (HSCA), undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Janos, Leo, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Clark, Comer, Mexico, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Hudkins, Lonnie, 1963-1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Bustos-Videla, Charlotte Z., 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Acoustics (evidence in Kennedy Assassination), 1978-1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- HSCA Dissent (House Select Committee on Assassination Records), undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Scott, Winston, 1967-1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Flores, Daniel, 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Cubans, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Swenson, Harold/ “Langosch”, Joseph H., 1965-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Blakey, G. Robert, “201 file” CIA Memo, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Mitrokhin, Vasili, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Wofford, Harris, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Crozier, Ross, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Consejo Revolucionario Cubano, (Cuban Revolutionary Council) (CRC), 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- CIA, President’s Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board (PFIAB), undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
- CIA Documents, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Mexico City 1995 Release, 1960-1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Coleman, William T., Follow-Up (Foreign), 1964-1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Castro-Cuba, 1961-1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Fidel in Mexico, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Castro Speeches, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Castro + Cuba II, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
- AMMUG-1 (Vladimir Rodriguez LaHera), undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Espinosa-Hernandez, Victor (Rolando Cubela(s)), undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kennedy, Robert Francis (Bobby), 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Kennedy, Robert Francis, excerpts from Of Kennedys and Kings, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Haig, Jr., General Al, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Kennedy, Robert Francis/CIA, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Mexico City, Photos, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Lopez, Gilberto (Policarpo-Lopez, Gilberto), 1963-1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Track 1, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Gordon, Lt. Com. John, 1964-1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Hemming, Gerald Patrick, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Church, Frank, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- CIA Response to Church, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- CIA 1975 Assassination Review (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Corso, Philip, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Ford, Charles, 1962-1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Bishop, Maurice, Mexico City, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- King, Joseph Caldwell (J.C.), “Thy Will be Done”, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Shackley, Ted, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Piccolo, Joseph, 1957-1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Sanchez, Nestor, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Fitzgerald, Desmond, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Halpern, Sam, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Philby, Harold Adrian Russell “Kim”, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Russian Assassination File, 1959-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Harvey, William “Bill” King (testimony before Church CommitteeDLAlleged Assn. Plots Involving Foreign Leaders, 1975) (Box 4, Folder 5)
- AMTRUNK Operation, 1963-1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Operation 40, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Bay of Pigs, 1962-1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Esterline, Jake, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Project ZRRIFLE, 1962-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- QJ/WIN (a.k.a. QJWIN) (codename) (Mankel, Jose), 1960-1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Kangles, Constantine “Gus”, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
- JFK Cuba Policy, 1961-1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Rothman, Norman, 1961-1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Guevara, Che + JFK, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Maheu, Robert, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Cuba Track One, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Rostow, Walt W., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Cuba Planning, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Cuba and the Kennedys, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Missiles + Cuba (Cuban Missile Crisis), 1962-1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Cuban Exiles, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- McLaney, Michael “Mike” J., 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Interpen (Intercontinental Penetration Force), undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Pfeiffer, Jack B./Bay of Pigs, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Hawkins, Col. Jack, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Rex Affair/Bayo-Pawley Affair, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Bissell, Richard, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Cuba and Castro, General, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
- “Scelso, John” (John Whitten), undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Angleton, James, 1953-1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Hand, Frank, 1953-1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Ayers, Captain Bradley, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Langosch, Joseph, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Hidalgo, Barney, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Brugioni, Dino, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Helms, Richard, 1962-1998 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Helms on plots, 1975-1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Hurwitch, Ambassador Robert Arnold, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Dungan, Ralph A., undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Dungan Memo, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Deneslya, Donald, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- CIA Debrief of LHO (Lee Harvey Oswald), undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Dulles, Hon. Allen W. and the Kennedys, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Kryptos (sculpture), undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- President’s Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board (PFIAB), 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Odio, Sylvia, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Odio, Sylvia, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Ford, Charles, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Defectors, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Archives, Electronic, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
- National Archives, Missing + Withheld, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- National Archives, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
- U-2 Incident + Paris Summit, 1977-1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1979-1995 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Ike’s Farewell, Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Chicago Conference, JFK assassination symposium, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- King, Jr., Martin Luther; Kimble, J. R., 1977-1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Washington Post, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Sixth Floor, JFK Assassination Exhibit, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Research Methods, Private Investigation, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Eyewitness Testimony, Methods and Research, 1993-1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 1989-1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- “JFK Records Collection Act of 1992DLAdvisory Committee”, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- McNamara, Robert, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Coalition On Political Assassinations (COPA), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- “Camelot Documents”/White, Theodore H. (T. H.), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Letters Out, Information Requests, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- JFK Advisors, 1963-1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Dallas Coverage, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Lobster, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Kennedy Psyche, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
- “The Nation”/ Holland, Max, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Burke, Richard, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Voss, Dr. Marlyn William, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Burkley, Dr. George G., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Oswald, Marina, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Fake Defectors, 1963-1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Ryder, Dial, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Zapruder, Abraham (Film), 1963-1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Permindex/BCCI (Permanent Industrial Expositions)/(Bank of Credit and Commerce International), 1957-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Phelper, Ben, 1964-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Porter, Rachel (Oswald), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Simpson, O’Wighton Delk (Jr.), 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Sturgis, Frank, 1975-1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Presidential Motorcade Schematic Listing (PMSL), 1963, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Futrell, Captain Al, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Halfen, Jack, 1957-1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Herald, Jerry, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Frazier, Buell Wesley “B.W.”, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Aase, Jean (a.k.a. Jean West), 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Reynolds, Don B., 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Witnesses/Suspects, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Magazine Articles, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Magazine Articles, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Magazine Articles, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Coup d’état in America, by Canfield and Weberman, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- The National Tattler, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Strange Deaths, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Craig, Roger D., 1983 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Crichton, Jack A., undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Crisman, Fred Lee, 1969-1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Culligan, Roland B. “Bud”, 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Curington, John + H. L. Hunt, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Davis, Tom E. (III), 1963-1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Gabaldin, Guy, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
- The Men Behind the Guns (by W.R. Morris)+ Harry Dean, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Delgado, Nelson, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Gharis, Charles “Chas” M., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Garrison Tape, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Garrison, Jim, 1967-1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Giesbrecht, Richard (article by Peter R. Whitney), 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Gorman, Evelyn, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Gritz, Bo, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Harrelson, Charles, 1981-1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Hartman, Wayne E., and Edna, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Hemming, Gerry, 1962-1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Hendrix, Harold “Hal” Victor, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Hess, Diane “Didi”, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Hill, Jean, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Holt, Chauncey Marvin, 1963-1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Hughes, Howard/ “Puppetmaster” + Watergate, 1975-1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Hughes still(s), undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Hundley, William, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Hunt, E. H./Victor Marchetti, 1973-1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Hunt Letter, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Kennedy, Joe, Corruption, 1960-1991 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Nagell, Richard C., 1955-1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Nelson, R.C., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Nix, Orville, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Norris, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Norton, Donald P., 1967, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Odom, Lee, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Otepka, Otto, 1970, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- O’Neill, Jr., Thomas “Tip” Phillip, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Simpson, O’Wighton Delk + Hess, Diane “DiDi”, 1965-1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Simpson, O’Wighton Delk + Hess, Diane “DiDi”, 1965-1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Simpson, O’Wighton Delk + Hess, Diane “DiDi”, Audio Tape, 1965-1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Oswald, Lee Harvey, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Oswald, Lee Harvey + Fair Play for Cuba Committee (FPCC), Literature, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Plumlee, William Robert “Bob”, 1959-1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Plumlee, William Robert (a.k.a. Tosh, William Pearson, William Payne), 1959-1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Harlandale House (3126 Harlandale Avenue, Dallas, TX), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Counter Intelligence Program (COINTELPRO) + Socialist Workers Party, 1961-1980 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Oswald, Lee Harvey, Defense Department (DD) 1173 ID Card, Military Identification, 1956-1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Alba, Adrian, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Bucknell, David Milton + Botehlo, Judge James “Jim”, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Alderisio, Philip “Phil”, 1963-1964 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Allman, Pierce, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Alexander, Asst. DA William “Bill”, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Armsted, Jerry, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Angers, Brad J., 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Attwood, William, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Augustinovich, Ronald Lee, 1969, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Bagley, Tennent Peter, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Bishop, William “Bill”, 1963-1988 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Bolden, Abraham “Abe” + Chicago, 1963-1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Braden, Eugene Hale “Jim”, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Brandle, Mary Jane, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Brengel, Mary Helen Stanford, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Braverman, A. Marvin, 1950-1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Bronson, Charles L. + window, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Bullock, Milton, 1957, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Byford, Charles, 1961-1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Cancellare photo + Tilson, Jr., Tom, 1978-1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Castellanos, Ernesto, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Castorr, Colonel L. Robert, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Cheramie, Rose, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Cleontes, Robert, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Click, Daryl, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Clinton, Louisiana, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Cobb, Richard, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Collins, Frederick “Fred” J., undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Connally, Governor John, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Cooper, Marion M., 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Cooper, Marion M., 1955-1992 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Rodriguez Orcabrerro, Manuel, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Oswald, Marina, 1962-1993 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Owen, Dr. Wayne + Cherami, Rose, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Patterson, Robert Kermit, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Pena, Orest, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Lorenz, Marita, 1963-1993 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Kennedy, Robert F. (RFK), undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
- de Mohrenschildt, George, 1963-1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Government Secrecy, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Government Censorship, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Walker, Edwin A., 1960-1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- French Connection, 1975, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Oswald, Lee HarveyDLCIA File, 1959-1963 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Oswald, Lee HarveyDLLeft Handed?, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Oswald, Lee HarveyDLMotive (Davison and Cockburn), 1983, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Josh Butler & Co., undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Dinkin, Eugene B., 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Morrow, Hubert A., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- King, John J., 1963-1970 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Maasdam (MS Maasdam Cruise ship), undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Reynolds, Harold, 1963, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Korth, Fred and Kemp, Billy, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Conflict, “The Dorff Report”, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), 1979-1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Books, Video, etc., 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- The Rebel, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Reviews (Television and Book), undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Wasky, Donald, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Hall, Loran, 1968-1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Wheat, Clinton, 1968-1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Journal of the American Medical Association, 1981-1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Schmidt, Volkmar, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Air Force One, 1963, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- House Committee on Government Operations Legislation and National Security Committee, Hearings, 1983-1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Wood, Sterling + Rifle Range, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Slack, Garland, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Lee, Herbert Leon, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Jones, Candy, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Beckley Tenants, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Cash, Ben and Preston, Billy J., 1964, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- House Select Committee on Assassinations (HSCA), Tapes, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Kennedy, Robert F., Investigation, 1965-1978 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Vaganov, Igor “Turk”, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Underhill, Gary, 1964-1977 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Trapnell, Garrett, 1963-1964, 1972, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- The “Tramps:" Harold Doyle, John Forrester Gedney, Gus Abrams, 1963, 1968-1969, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Tittle, Roger, 1963, 1982, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Tower, Senator John, 1962-1964, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Russell, Robert Lawrence, 1978, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Schrand, Martin E., 1958, 1963, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Saggue, Tauler, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Russo, Perry, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Rorke, Jr., Alexander I., 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Richard, Jr., Bert, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Quiroga, Carlos, 1963, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Prouty, L. Fletcher “Fletch”, 1963-1964, 1975, 1986, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Vallee, Thomas Arthur, 1963, 1967-1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Walter, William, Teletype, 1963, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Wade, Henry, 1968, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Valenti, Jack, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- McKeown, Robert, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
- McDonald, Hugh, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Mason, Bernice, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Masen, John Thomas, 1960, 1964-1969, 1976, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- The Babushka Lady, 1964, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB): Release Advisories, Media Advisories, News Releases (1 of 2), 1995-1999 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Assassination Records Review Board (ARRB): Release Advisories, Media Advisories, News Releases (2 of 2), 1995-1999 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- ARRB: 1996 Report, Federal Register, Public Law, 1992, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- ARRB: Clippings, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- ARRB: Documents, 1963, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- LA Free Press + Flynt, Larry, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)